Hello everyone, I am Adil Islam
the Chief of Staff at Stability AI
my team collaborate with AWS on groundbreaking solutions including SageMaker and Bedrock
I'd like to take a moment to talk about one of our ongoing collaborative projects
Stable Diffusion AWS Extension
you can find on GitHub at the link shown on the screen
This project represents a leap forward in our collaboration
combining Stability's expertise in AI with AWS's robust cloud infrastructure
users can migrate existing inference and training workload from standalone local client to AWS SageMaker
with optimized efficiency on scaling and cost
It's also helpful to promote Stable Diffusion to the broader open source community
At Stability AI, we're helping to build an ecosystem where everyone can benefit from our advancements
thanks to open source
And we are grateful to have AWS as our partner at this journey
Looking ahead, we're excited about the potential for even deeper collaboration
One area we're particularly excited about is the integration of our new SDXL model with AWS SageMaker
This integration will allow us to leverage the full power of AWS's machine learning capabilities
opening up new possibilities for innovation and customer value
Finally, I want to express my deep gratitude to both the Stability AI and AWS teams
Your hard work, dedication and creativity are what make this collaboration so successful
Thank you for all that you do.